Lombard GIC Q4 earning PAT jumps 7% YOY
to 547 crore
and 7 per share dividend declared. Total
income stood at
uh 6618.76
crore during the quarter under review
reflecting a 17.12% YOY jumps from
5651.71
17 crore in the March quarter
of the 2024 to 2025 fiscal year, Q4
financial 25.
And ICICI Lombard GIC has a total market
capitalization of 92
921.11
crore as of April 15
2026 according to data on the NSE.
And ICICI Lombard GIC Q4 earning ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company GIC
posted a 7.25%
YOY
increases in its profit after tax to
546.56
crore for the fourth quarter of the 2025
to 2026 financial year
Q4 financial 26.
In the corresponding period of the
previous fiscal year it logged a profit
of 595.59 crore it reported an
irregularity
filing date Wednesday April 15. And its
total income stood at 6618.76
crore during the quarter under review
reflecting a 17.12%
YOY jumps from the 5651.7
crore in the March quarter of the 2024
to 2025
fiscal year, Q4 financial 25.
ICICI Bank General Insurance arms also
recorded a
10.28% YOY growth in its the net premium
earned at
uh Uh, rest 5790.53
crore for the March quarter of financial
year 2026 compared to 5225.58
crore in the same period of financial
year 2025.
It is combined ratios stood at 101.2%
from the reporting quarter in comparison
with 102.5%
It is locking the fourth quarter of
financial year 2025.
The combined ratio insurance measures in
insures and underwriting profitability
by adding incurred losses and expensive
then dividing by earned premiums.
Dividend recommended ICICI Lombard GIC
Board of director also recommended a
final
dividend of seven per equity share at
the rest of
17% which face value of 10 each for the
financial year ended March 31, 2026
subject to the approval of the member of
the company at the ensuing annual
general meeting AGM.